[
    {
      "question": "Bootstrap 3 is mobile-first.",
      "option": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class provides a responsive fixed width container?",
      "option": [
        ".container-fluid",
        ".container",
        ".container-fixed"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class provides a full width container, spanning the entire width of the viewport?",
      "option": [
        ".container-fluid",
        ".container-fixed",
        ".container"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "The Bootstrap grid system is based on how many columns?",
      "option": [
        "3",
        "6",
        "12",
        "9"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class adds zebra-stripes to a table?",
      "option": [
        ".table-bordered",
        ".table-striped",
        ".even and .odd",
        ".table-zebra"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class shapes an image to a circle?",
      "option": [
        ".img-round",
        ".img-circle",
        ".img-thumbnail",
        ".img-rounded"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a big box for calling extra attention?",
      "option": [
        ".jumbotron",
        ".bigbox",
        ".container"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which button class is used to create a large button?",
      "option": [
        ".btn-lg",
        ".btn-l",
        ".btn-xl",
        ".btn-large"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a button group?",
      "option": [
        ".button-group",
        ".group-btn",
        ".group-button",
        ".btn-group"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "How can you insert a search icon?",
      "option": [
        "<span class=\"glyph glyph-search\"></span>",
        "<span class=\"glyphicon glyphicon-search\"></span>",
        "<span class=\"glyphicon search\"></span>",
        "<span class=\"glyphicon-search\"></span>"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a badge?",
      "option": [
        ".tag",
        ".label",
        ".badge",
        ".flag"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a basic pagination?",
      "option": [
        ".navigation",
        ".page",
        ".pages",
        ".pagination"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a basic list group?",
      "option": [
        ".group-list",
        ".grouped-list",
        ".list-group"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class adds a heading to a panel?",
      "option": [
        ".panel-heading",
        ".panel-head",
        ".panel-header",
        ".panel-footer"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class indicates a dropdown menu?",
      "option": [
        ".select",
        ".dropdown",
        ".dropdown-list"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "A standard navigation tab is created with:",
      "option": [
        "<ul class=\"nav nav-tabs\">",
        "<ul class=\"nav tabs\">",
        "<ul class=\"nav nav-navbar\">",
        "<ul class=\"navigation-tabs\">"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "A standard navigation bar is created with:",
      "option": [
        "<nav class=\"navigationbar navbar-default\">",
        "<nav class=\"navbar default-navbar\">",
        "<nav class=\"navbar navbar-default\">",
        "<nav class=\"nav navbar\">"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a black navigation bar?",
      "option": [
        ".navbar-black",
        ".navbar-default",
        ".navbar-inverse",
        ".navbar-dark"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which plugin is used to cycle through elements, like a slideshow?",
      "option": [
        "Orbit",
        "Slideshow",
        "Carousel",
        "Scrollspy"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which plugin is used to create a modal window?",
      "option": [
        "Popup",
        "Window",
        "Dialog Box",
        "Modal"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which plugin is used to create a tooltip?",
      "option": [
        "Modal",
        "Dialog Box",
        "Tooltip",
        "Popup"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which contextual class indicates a succesful or positive action?",
      "option": [
        ".text-warning",
        ".text-success",
        ".text-info",
        ".text-primary"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which contextual class indicates a dangerous or potentially negative action?",
      "option": [
        ".text-warning",
        ".text-info",
        ".text-danger",
        ".text-primary"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class indicates uppercased text?",
      "option": [
        ".ucase",
        ".uppercase",
        ".text-capitalize",
        ".text-uppercase"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "The Bootstrap grid system works across multiple devices.",
      "option": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    }
  ]